Finding Aid for the John Egerton Papers - Estate Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Writings
  - Writings by Others - 1815 by Tony Dunbar, n.d. - Pp. 105-231 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Writings by Others - The Madhi by Bob Wickersham, n.d. - Pp. 1-95 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Writings by Others - The Madhi by Bob Wickersham, n.d. - Pp. 96-181 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Writings by Others - The Madhi by BobWickersham, n.d. - Pp. 182-299 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Writings by Others - The Madhi by Bob Wickersham. n.d. - Pp. 300-425 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Subject Files
  - Subject Files - “A Complete Index to the American Slave” (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Subject Files - “Seeking a Way Out: Services and Challenges Affecting Tennessee’s Poor” (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Subject Files - “Hank Williams, Garth Brooks, BR5-49?” (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Subject Files - “Our Ancestors Were Engineers”, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Subject Files - “Dixie’s War: The South and Word War II”, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Subject Files - Race Relations - Miscellaneous Articles, 1980s (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Subject Files - Race Relations - Miscellaneous Articles, 1990s (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Subject Files - Race Relations - Articles from The Chronicle of Higher Education, 1990s (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Subject Files - Race Relations - Percentage of Black Population in Eleven Southern States, 1970s and 1980s - Two Maps (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Subject Files - “Race Relations and Ethnicity”, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Subject Files - “Racial Issues in Campus Life”, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Subject Files - “Remedies for Racial Inequality”, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Subject Files - Miscellaneous Articles, 1990s-2000s (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Subject Files - Nashville School Desegregation Materials (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Subject Files - Research Materials for a Proposed Book about John Kasper (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Subject Files - Research Materials for Proposed Book about John Kasper (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Subject Files - Research Materials for a Proposed Book about John Kasper (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Subject files - Research Materials for a Proposed Book about John Kasper (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Subject Files - Research Materials for a Proposed Book about John Kasper (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Subject Files - Nashville School Board Election, District 8, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Subject Files - Materials Pertaining to TVA, 1950s-1990s (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Subject Files - Articles about Music, 1990s-2000s (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Subject Files - Materials Pertaining to Metro Nashville Archives (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Subject Files - Materials Pertaining to Metro Nashville Archives (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Subject Files - Materials Pertaining to Metro Nashville Archives (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Subject Files - Materials Pertaining to Metro Nashville Archives (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Subject files - Materials Pertaining to Metro Nashville Archives (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Personal
  - Personal Information - Publicity Photos (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Personal Information - Publicity Photos (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Personal Information - Publicity Photos (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Personal Information - Publicity Photos (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Personal Information - Resumes, Job Searches (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Personal Information - Honors Awarded (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Personal Information - Memorial Service and Tributes for John Egerton (1935-2013) (Box 35, Folder 7)